<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2010 The Android Open Source Project

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->

<resources>
    <string-array name="tips">
        <item>Welcome to LineageOS, click for other tips</item>
        <item>Privay guard helps you protect your private data from installed apps</item>
        <item>Protected apps will restrict access to apps with private data by adding a pattern</item>
        <item>Live display optimizes your screen basing on the time of the day and ambient conditions</item>
        <item>Double tap the status bar to turn the screen off</item>
        <item>Yer lookin\' for teh Br0tips? Call\'em</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="br0tips" translatable="false">
        <item>Want some more home screens?\nSwipe left and right to find them\n(No theft required)</item>
        <item>Ballmer Peak: Optimal coding ability takes place between a BAC of .129 and .138.</item>
        <item>GUYS, GUYS, 0 times 0 is ALWAYS 0</item>
        <item>Home is a garden: touch &amp; hold an empty spot to grow new icons</item>
        <item>Always catproof your electronics, cats are bound to pee on them</item>
        <item>Touch Market for apps. Like a box of chocolates, each one a surprise</item>
        <item>Don\'t listen to Dr Kmobs. He is a real doctor, but that is not a thermometer</item>
        <item>Kmobs is actually a doctor now! But that is still not a stethoscope</item>
        <item>For 100\u0025 Minnesotan, add baijiu to invisiblek</item>
        <item>For \"white guy dancing\" add decad3nce and broncos</item>
        <item>Can\'t stop won\'t stop</item>
        <item>We tried to butter toastcfh and drop him to see if he landed right side up, but all we got was wimax</item>
        <item>Mama ciwrl knows best. Presents a choice, but decides for you anyway</item>
        <item>shareef is to telephony what giuliani is to cyber</item>
        <item>For over inflated ego, apply one maniac103 code review</item>
        <item>Code not complex enough? Add a layer of jruesga</item>
        <item>That\'s not a squatting unicorn, that\'s a squatting roman</item>
        <item>When nothing is broken, revamp it with some jrizzoli</item>
        <item>There has to be something about a cyanogen force push</item>
        <item>Want to see eventual collapse of society? Offset a pixel for kover and asher</item>
        <item>Steve had force push, then we forked</item>
        <item>Senyor doesn\'t speak spanish, but he does speak margaritas</item>
        <item>Some people say that psychoi3oy caught a fly with chopsticks, but no one has seen the JIRA ticket for it</item>
        <item>decad3nce: jaded since he started working at inc</item>
        <item>s0be was named before the drink failed, we have kernel commits to prove it</item>
        <item>Don\'t forget to keep your winzip up to date</item>
        <item>mikeioannina can only be translated in 14 languages, otherwise we have to gc gerrit</item>
        <item>Some people say arcee is older than the known universe. But we don\'t have the tools or the scotch to carbon date him</item>
        <item>Sorry, boss had a question. Now i can get back to work</item>
        <item>brinly, at his too young of age, has won more vulnerability bounties than Isaac Newton had created motion laws</item>
        <item>Development Process of Rashed:\n1. Find bug\n2. Get blocked by arceen\n3. Attempt to ask invisiblek for help\n4. <b>???</b>\n5. panel.sh</item>
        <item>bbiab: i need food</item>
        <item>Shipit and buy donuts later</item>
        <item>Gotta hax that</item>
        <item>decad3nce: more tequila please</item>
        <item>decad3nce: oh god, not tequila</item>
        <item>When stuff is working too well, add a bit of javelinanddart</item>
        <item>rashed: Works 100\u0025, except those 9 of 10 features</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
